# Rafael Galdino da Silva

rafaelgaldinosilva81@gmail.com · +55 88998672126 · https://rafaeldev.me

I'm a focused and self-taught professional that loves and studies programming for more than 3 years and acting as a freelancer. I've been learning modern web technologies for a year in search of a position to kickstart my career. I like to build websites that are beaultiful, performative, functional and I am, for sure, the best choice for your company.

### **EDUCATION**

# EEEP Amélia Figueiredo de Lavor

Feb 2017 - Dec 2019

IT Technician with focus on web programming

### Universidade Federal do Ceará

Feb 2020 - 2024 (Expected)

Bachelor's degree on Computer Science

GPA: 9.15

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# iTarget - IT Trainee

Iguatu, CE

Development of an internal app to manage electronic documents using PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery

Remote

### **Freelancer** - Fullstack Developer

Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

Development of an official registry office webpage, used for divulgation of services, available at https://www.costalima1oficio.com.br/

Jan 2019 - Present

 Development of personal pages, blogs, landing pages and commercial sites using PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Wordpress, etc.

### TECH SKILLS

Main: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, PHP.

Libraries and Frameworks: React.js, Node.js, Express, Next.js, Prisma, TailwindCSS, etc.

Databases: MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL.

Tools: Git, Github, Figma, Docker, Firebase, Supabase, Vercel

**Languages:** Native portuguese, Proficient English (C2 Standard English Test)

### MAIN COURSES

**Bootcamp Orange Tech** + Digital Innovation One

Resume: HTML/CSS, ReactJS, Javascript, Typescript, Versionamento, Agile

Front-end development Libraries FreeCodeCamp

Resume: Development of 5 projects using ReactJS, TailwindCSS

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

Markpad - NextJS, TailwindCSS, Prisma, PostgreSOL, Supabase Free markdown editor with real-time preview and sharing capabilities https://markpad.vercel.app/

Mydrive - ReactJS, TailwindCSS, Firebase

Cloud storage service like Google Drive, One drive, etc.

https://github.com/rafaelsilva81/mydrive

Raijin - NextJS, TailwindCSS, Prisma, PostgreSQL, Supabase Free and simple link shortener

https://raijin.tk

MyCalendar - ReactJS, TailwindCSS, NodeJS, MongoDB, Prisma Single-page-application for an agenda where you can manage tasks daily/weekly/monthly

https://github.com/rafaelsilva81/spa-calendark